<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>paralune</title>
    <link>http://paralune.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on paralune</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2017 18:19:22 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://paralune.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Mythic Ocean</title>
      <link>http://paralune.com/mythic-ocean/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2017 18:19:22 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://paralune.com/mythic-ocean/</guid>
      <description>About the Game Mythic Ocean is a single-player, first-person, underwater exploration game set in an otherworldly ocean. The idea for the game came from our mutual fascination with the sea - our love for its gentle beauty, and our fear of its darkest depths.
You&amp;rsquo;ll meet many strange creatures, and what you say to them will have a big impact on how they feel about you and each other. The mystery of where this world came from - and where it&amp;rsquo;s headed - will become clearer as you form bonds with its inhabitants and help them grow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Mythic Ocean</title>
      <link>http://paralune.com/2017/08/announcing-mythic-ocean/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2017 16:29:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://paralune.com/2017/08/announcing-mythic-ocean/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For the past year, Paralune has been hard at work on a game.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Keeping it a secret has been tough. So far we&amp;rsquo;ve focused on proving out our ideas and teaching ourselves all the necessary skills to make it happen, but now we&amp;rsquo;re finally ready to share our first project: &lt;strong&gt;Mythic Ocean.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s a brief teaser video: 
&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; padding-top: 30px; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;//www.youtube.com/embed/dHriVqfqDMI&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%;&#34; allowfullscreen frameborder=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started</title>
      <link>http://paralune.com/2017/08/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 03:41:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://paralune.com/2017/08/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We were brought together by a shared desire to tell interactive stories. We want our games to be accessible yet mysterious, with a strong emotional impact and an experience unique to each player.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://paralune.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2017 03:25:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://paralune.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Paralune is a 3-person game studio in Austin, TX, founded in 2016 with the purpose of creating emotional stories with deep interactivity.
Exploring the thoughts and feelings of the characters in our games is our focus, and players will be asked to make choices that have real consequences. Our players are storytellers, too.
Our first title is currently unannounced and in development, so follow us on social media to get regular updates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jobs</title>
      <link>http://paralune.com/jobs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2017 03:25:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://paralune.com/jobs/</guid>
      <description>We don&amp;rsquo;t have any open positions right now, but in the future they&amp;rsquo;ll be posted on this page.
Regardless, we would love to hear from you &amp;ndash; just send your resume (and website/portfolio if applicable) to contact@paralune.com.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>